A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Diane Van Wie, Series 34 FA373
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Diane Van Wie, Series 34
1953-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
Van Wie, Diane
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller)
FA373
91.59 Cubic Feet
Biographical/Historical note
Nelson A. Rockefeller served as governor of New York from January 1, 1959, to December 18, 1973. He was the first person elected to four consecutive four-year terms as a state governor.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 15 34
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement note
This series is divided into 12 subseries:
Subseries 1 - Campaign Correspondence, 1964-1968. Subseries 2 - Subject Files, 1953-1973. Subseries 3 - Acknowledgements of Support Gubernatorial/National, 1968-1970. Subseries 4 - Executive Chamber Staff Memos, 1962-1973. Subseries 5 - Latin American Trip, 1969-1970. Subseries 6 - Meetings, Luncheons, and Dinners, 1958-1973. Subseries 7 - Nelson Rockefeller Schedule, 1958-1970. Subseries 8 - Position Papers and Policy Proposals, 1959-1964. Subseries 9 - Social Files, 1959-1963. Subseries 10 - Political Files, 1958-1972. Subseries 11 - Miscellaneous Files, 1958-1973. Subseries 12 - Executive Chamber Correspondence, 1970-1973.
Scope and Contents note
NOTE TO RESEARCHERS
This series contains the office files of Diane Van Wie. They document official activities in the execution of her duties as a member of Nelson A. Rockefeller's staff. The actions, decisions, and exchanges of information or points of view documented here occurred in the course of proposing and implementing policies for the Rockefeller administration, political campaigns, and/or Rockefeller's personal activities. However, unless a document is specifically addressed to or from Nelson A. Rockefeller, or is referred to in a document addressed to him, it should not be assumed that he saw the document or was aware of its existence or substance. Furthermore, researchers should bear in mind that staff files may contain documents or drafts addressed to Rockefeller that were never shown to him.
SCOPE AND CONTENT
This series documents portions of Nelson A. Rockefeller's public activities from 1953 to 1973. Diane Van Wie was on Nelson A. Rockefeller's executive staff prior to and while he was Governor of New York. She was one of two assistants to Ann Whitman, executive assistant to the governor, in the Albany office.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Appointments Office (FA353)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Assembly and Senate Memos (FA354)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Joseph H. Boyd (FA355)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, James Cannon (FA356)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Affirmative Action (N. Lee Cook) (FA357)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Counsel's Office (FA358)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York State Committee to Reelect the President (FA359)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Jerry A. Danzig (FA360)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Executive Chamber (FA361)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, 55th Street (FA362)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Issue Books (FA363)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Arthur Massolo (FA364)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Hugh Morrow (FA242)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Office (FA365)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Civil Service Resolutions (Charles H. Palmer) (FA366)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Political Files (FA367)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Press Office (FA368)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Public Relations (FA369)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Departmental Reports (FA370)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, William J. Ronan (FA371)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Speeches (FA372)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Ann C. Whitman, Gubernatorial (FA374)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Gene Wyckoff (FA375)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Republican State Fund Raising Reports (FA376)
State governments -- United States; Public relations; Vice-Presidents -- United States; United States; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1966; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1962; Public policy; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Federal government -- United States; Economics; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1958; Government policy; Civil defense -- United States; Civil defense; Civil service -- New York (State); Civil service; International economic relations; Human rights; International relations -- United States; International relations; Arms control; Arms control -- United States; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970; Affirmative action programs -- New York (State); Political science; Political campaigns -- United States; Presidential campaigns -- United States; Legislation -- New York (State); Latin America; New York (State); New York (N.Y.)
- Campaign Correspondence, 1964-1968; 01; 16 document box(es)
  Arrangement note
  This subseries is arranged alphabetically by state, and alphabetically by addressee thereunder.
  Scope and Contents note
  This subseries contains carbon copies of letters of thanks from Nelson A. Rockefeller to campaign workers, supporters, and well-wishers regarding his presidential campaigns in 1964 and 1968.
  - Campaign Correspondence - Alabama (A-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Alaska (A-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Arizona (A-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Arkansas (A-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (A), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Al), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (As), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (B), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Be), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Bi), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Bo), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Bu), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (C), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ce), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ci), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Co), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Cu), 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (D), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (E), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Fa), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Fe), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Fi), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Fo), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Fu), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ga), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ge), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Gi), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Go), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Gu), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ha), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (He), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Hi), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ho), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Hu), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (I-J), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ka), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ke), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ki), 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ko), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ku), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (La), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Le), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Li), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Lo), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Lu), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Ma), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Mc), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Me), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Mi), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Mo), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Mu), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (N), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (O), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (P), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Q), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (R), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Sa), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Sc), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Se), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Sh), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Si-Sl), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Sm-Sp), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (St-Sz), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (T), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (U), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (V), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (W), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (We), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Wi), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (Wo), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Campaign Correspondence - California (X-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Colorado (A-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (A), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (B), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (C), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (D), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (E), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (F), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (G), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (H), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (I), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (J), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (K), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (L), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (M), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (N), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (O), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (P), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (Q), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (R), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (S), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (T), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Connecticut (U-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Delaware, 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (A), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (B), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (C), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (D), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (E), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (F), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (G), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (H), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (J), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (K), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (L), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (M), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (N), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (O), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (P), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (R), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (S), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (T), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Florida (V-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Georgia, 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Hawaii, 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Idaho, 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 116)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (A), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 117)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (B), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 118)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (C), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 119)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (D), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 120)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (E), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 121)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (F), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 122)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (G), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 123)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (H), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 124)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (I), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 125)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (J), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (K), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 127)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (L), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (M), 1964-1968 (Box 5, Folder 129)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (N), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 130)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (O), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 131)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (P), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 132)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (R), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 133)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (S), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 134)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (T), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Illinois (U-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Indiana, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Iowa, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Kansas, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Kentucky, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 140)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Louisiana, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 141)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Maine (A), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Maine (B), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 143)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Maine (C), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 144)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Maine (D), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 145)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Maine (E-G), 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 146)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Maine (H-K), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Maine (L-O), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 148)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Maine (P-S), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Maine (T-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Maryland (A-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (A), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (B), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (C), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (D), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (E), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (F), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (G), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 158)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (H), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (I), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (J), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 0160A)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (K), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (L), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (M), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (N), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (O), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (P), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 166)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (Q-R), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (S), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Massachusetts (T-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (A), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 170)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (B), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 171)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (C), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 172)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (D), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 173)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (E), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 174)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (F), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 175)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (G), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 176)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (H), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (J), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (K), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (L), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (M), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (N), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (O), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (P), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 184)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (R), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (S), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Michigan (T-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Minnesota, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Mississippi, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Missouri, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Montana, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Nebraska, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Campaign Correspondence - Nevada, 1964-1968 (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (A), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 194)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (B), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 195)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (C), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 196)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (D), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 197)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (E), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 198)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (F), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 199)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (G), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 200)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (H), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 201)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (I), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 202)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (J), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 203)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (K), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 204)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (L), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 205)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (M), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 206)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (N), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 207)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (O), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 208)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (P), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 209)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (Q), 1964-1968 (Box 9, Folder 210)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (R), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 211)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (S), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 212)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (T), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 213)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (U-V), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 214)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (W), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 215)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Hampshire (X-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 216)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (A), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 217)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (B), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 218)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (C), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 219)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (D), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 220)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (E), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 221)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (F), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 222)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (G), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 223)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (H), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 224)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (I-J), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 225)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (K), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 226)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (L), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 227)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (M), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 228)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (N-O), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 229)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (P), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 230)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (Q-R), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 231)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (S), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 232)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Jersey (T-Z), 1964-1968 (Box 10, Folder 233)
  - Campaign Correspondence - New Mexico, 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 234)